Thank you for watching!
The next day
Good morning
We arrived at Hamagawa
Thank you
Good morning.
The puddle is big.
It's a rainy day.
It's going to be sunny.
I forgot to bring an umbrella.
What's that?
A mole?
I didn't know that.
The puddle is big.
I'm going to cross the river.
There might be a four-leaf clover.
I'm looking for a four-leaf clover.
Franco
rea
bar
how
dangerous
,
The beginning.
The last one is Yui!
5,4,3,2,1
Yui is the last one!
Yui's last one is Yui!
I love you.
What should I do to make you look back?
I thought I had to change myself more.
I thought so.
Titanic.
I love you.
We are Super TAKIMEKI!
Oh, I see.
Oh, the sun is coming out!
It's sunny.
The sun is shining.
Mind blowing!
They have dep regel it
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm about to burst, I can't take it
anymore, I can't take it anymore
Just like it's going to be tied
someday... ahh
lol
She is so cute
I can't sleep anymore, I can't hold it
in
You're suddenly showing up
This is the north wind
This is the south wind
I don't know, it's random
Please subscribe to my channel!
I look strong.
I thought so.
I look like a space suit.
This is not a space suit.
I asked her which one is the most
expensive one among the bench coats she
prepared.
She said this one.
So, I bought this one.
It seems that she said that she would
buy only this one in spring.
When she chooses one.
It looks like a reflector.
It's a reflector.
It makes me bright.
It's a self-reflector.
Self-reflector.
It's the best.
This is the best one.
One more time.
Covered in sunshine!
It's 1pm.
I'm fashionweek!
It's cute.
It's a vintage coat.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I look like I'm wearing a mask.
Bye bye!
I love you!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm HAACHAN.
I love you.
Thank you for watching.
I can't take it anymore, I can't hold
it in
I love you.
How many pairs oflished are there in
this corner?​
In the final phase, what's the action
units that use it?​
I wonder... what will happen?​
Thank you for watching!
I love you.
Ah, I'm about to burst, I can't hold it
anymore
This is the most nervous I've ever been
I like you, I like you, I like you, I
like you
That's awkward!
The flied fish enrolls in two pockets.
It looks useful.
It's different.
Wow.
It can store a bunch of exacts.
They're finding their places.
Ypurai suggests a place
they can train at.
That feels unstoppable
It works
I can't stop
E
I ate
Strange!
It's lunch break.
Lunch break.
I'm so hungry that I can't eat.
I heard that there is a lunch box, so I
ate it.
How many meals do you want to eat
today?
Two meals.
I ate a lot.
There is a small piece of meat.
I ate a small piece of meat.
I ate it normally.
I think I ate too much.
I thought it was in the car.
It's higher than before.
It's good.
I'm happy.
We finished the shooting of the music
video.
Great!
It's amazing.
It's a special day.
We're going to have a TV commercial.
Wow!
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
We're going to make the world full of
love.
I'm so happy to be a happy commercial
director.
I'm so happy.
I think this commercial is always
watched by people who support us in the
countryside.
I hope this commercial will reach
everyone all over the country.
Please support us.
Please look forward to it.
We're waiting for your report.
Please tweet us on SNS.
Please look forward to it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
With the broadcasting schedule, I've
decided who will arrive later, but…
Movie's being shot on a set Y then we
enthusiasm
Schedewed
My sister marginalized me because of a
scene shot done by a fan leader.
I'm scared!
You are a lucky girl!
I'm sorry!
It doesn't hurt at all.
I'm fine.
I thought you were done.
I'm sorry!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I wonder why, when I smile, it's as if
the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and feel
better
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if it's cold and wet from
somewhere again
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
There's still a view I don't know in
front of me
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
I'll draw a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll guide you
Now I can say it, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the rain
drops are ringing
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the rain
drops are ringing
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Lalalalala lalalalala
Please subscribe to our channel!